Inventory of the National Cattlemen’s Association records, 1898-2018
University of Wyoming. American Heritage Center.
- Photographic Material, Series XIII.
  - Photographs, Subseries 1.
    - Arizona Executive Meeting, Jacobs Lake and Fredonia, AZ, August 1948 (Box 588, Folder 8)
    - Arizona Meeting, undated (Box 588, Folder 9)
    - Auctions, 1950 (Box 588, Folder 10)
    - Australia, 1921-1927 (Box 588, Folder 11)
    - Beef Promotion, 1950s-1960s (Box 588, Folder 12)
    - Beef Promotion, 1950s-1970s (Box 589, Folders 1-2)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, Washington, D.C., May 13, 1975 (Box 589, Folder 3)
    - Board of Directors Meeting and Retailer Visits, March 1974 (Box 589, Folder 4)
    - Bent Prowers C + H Meet, undated (Box 589, Folder 5)
    - Bent Prowers County Meeting, Los Animas, CO, March 5, 1949 (Box 589, Folder 6)
    - Bent Prowers Stockgrowers Association, Las Animas, CO, February 22, 1942 (Box 589, Folder 7)
    - Biographical Photographs-“A,”, 1958, undated (Box 589, Folder 8)
    - Biographical Photographs-“B,” Babbitt-Brewster, 1948, undated (Box 589, Folder 9)
    - Biographical Photographs-“B,” Briscoe-Butts, 1948, undated (Box 589, Folder 10)
    - Biographical Photographs-Bambert, Loren, 1949, undated (Box 589, Folder 11)
    - Biographical Photographs-Bixby, Fred H., undated (Box 589, Folder 12)
    - Biographical Photographs-Boice, Henry G., undated (Box 589, Folder 13)
    - Biographical Photographs-Boies, Oren F., undated (Box 589, Folder 14)
    - Biographical Photographs-Brite, Lucas C., 1928 (Box 589, Folder 15)
    - Biographical Photographs-Brock, L. Elmer, undated (Box 589, Folder 16)
    - Biographical Photographs-Brownfield, A.D., undated (Box 589, Folder 17)
    - Biographical Photographs-“C,”, undated (Box 589, Folder 18)
    - Biographical Photographs-Culberson, Victor, undated (Box 590, Folder 1)
    - Biographical Photographs-“D,”, 1956, undated (Box 590, Folder 2)
    - Biographical Photographs-“E,”, undated (Box 590, Folder 3)
    - Biographical Photographs-“F,”, 1950s, undated (Box 590, Folder 4)
    - Biographical Photographs-“G,”, 1950s, undated (Box 590, Folder 5)
    - Biographical Photographs-“H,”, 1940s-1950s (Box 590, Folder 6)
    - Biographical Photographs-Hagenbarth, Frank J., undated (Box 590, Folder 7)
    - Biographical Photographs-Hall, Radford, undated (Box 590, Folder 8)
    - Biographical Photographs-Hansen, Clifford, undated (Box 590, Folder 9)
    - Biographical Photographs-Heard, Dwight B., undated (Box 590, Folder 10)
    - Biographical Photographs-“I,”, undated (Box 590, Folder 11)
    - Biographical Photographs-“J,”, 1925, undated (Box 590, Folder 12)
    - Biographical Photographs-Jastro, Henry A., undated (Box 590, Folder 13)
    - Biographical Photographs-Jones, Ralph, undated (Box 590, Folder 14)
    - Biographical Photographs-“K,”, 1964, undated (Box 590, Folder 15)
    - Biographical Photographs-Kendrick, John B., undated (Box 590, Folder 16)
    - Biographical Photographs-“L,”, undated (Box 590, Folder 17)
    - Biographical Photographs-“M,” MacFarlane-Mohler, 1920s-1950s (Box 590, Folder 18)
    - Biographical Photographs-“M,” Mollin-Murphy, 1920s-1950s (Box 590, Folder 19)
    - Biographical Photographs-Martin, Charles F., undated (Box 590, Folder 20)
    - Biographical Photographs-Milburn, G.R., undated (Box 590, Folder 21)
    - Biographical Photographs-Mitchell, Albert F., undated (Box 590, Folder 22)
    - Biographical Photographs-Mollin, F.E., 1929, undated (Box 591, Folder 1)
    - Biographical Photographs-“N,”, undated (Box 591, Folder 2)
    - Biographical Photographs-“O,”, 1958, undated (Box 591, Folder 3)
    - Biographical Photographs-O’Donel, C.M., 1947, undated (Box 591, Folder 4)
    - Biographical Photographs-“P,”, undated (Box 591, Folder 5)
    - Biographical Photographs-Pryor, Ike T., undated (Box 591, Folder 6)
    - Biographical Photographs-“R,”, 1950s, undated (Box 591, Folder 7)
    - Biographical Photographs-Radebaugh, Cushman S., undated (Box 591, Folder 8)
    - Biographical Photographs-“S,”, undated (Box 591, Folder 9)
    - Biographical Photographs-Smith, A.A., undated (Box 591, Folder 10)
    - Biographical Photographs-“T,”, undated (Box 591, Folder 11)
    - Biographical Photographs-“U,”, undated (Box 591, Folder 12)
    - Biographical Photographs-Unidentified Men, undated (Box 591, Folder 13)
    - Biographical Photographs-“V,”, undated (Box 591, Folder 14)
    - Biographical Photographs-“W,”, undated (Box 591, Folder 15)
    - Biographical Photographs-Watt, Joseph N., undated (Box 591, Folder 16)
    - Biographical Photographs-Wright, William B., 1948, undated (Box 591, Folder 17)
    - Biographical Photographs-“XYZ,”, undated (Box 591, Folder 18)
    - Blocked Roads, 1950s-1960s (Box 591, Folder 19)
    - Blythe Feed Yards, undated (Box 591, Folder 20)
    - Bonneville Dam, undated (Box 591, Folder 21)
    - Border States Meeting on Foot and Mouth Disease, Albuquerque, NM, April 21, 1947 (Box 591, Folder 22)
    - Boulder Stockgrowers Association, 1946 (Box 591, Folder 23)
    - Boulder County Stockgrowers Association, Lyons, CO, February 1947 (Box 591, Folder 24)
    - Brand Conference, 1951 (Box 591, Folder 25)
    - Brands and Branding, 1950s (Box 591, Folder 26)
    - Brazil, undated (Box 591, Folder 27)
    - Brush Burning-Madera County, CA, 1955 (Box 591, Folder 28)
    - Bryant Edwards Ranch, Henrietta, TX, 1949 (Box 591, Folder 29)
    - Buffalo, 1919-1938 (Box 592, Folder 1)
    - Buffalo, Daniels Park, CO, undated (Box 592, Folder 2)
    - Buildings, undated (Box 592, Folder 3)
    - Buildings-New, 1950s (Box 592, Folder 4)
    - By-The-Way Ranch, owned by Sam R. McKelvie, Valentine, NE, May 1948 (Box 592, Folder 5)
    - California Cattlemen’s Convention, San Jose, CA, December 1948 (Box 592, Folder 6)
    - California Cattlemen’s Association, Northern Tour, 1951 (Box 592, Folder 7)
    - California Cattlemen’s Convention, Red Bluff, CA, December 1955 (Box 592, Folder 8)
    - California Convention, Santa Cruz, CA, December 1953 (Box 592, Folder 9)
    - California Meeting Tour, September 1949 (Box 592, Folder 10)
    - California Tour, March 1950, November 1954, May 1955 (Box 592, Folders 11-13)
    - Calves in Now Mexico at Water Tank, 1951 (Box 592, Folder 14)
    - Canada, 1929, 1951 (Box 592, Folder 15)
    - Cartoons, undated (Box 592, Folder 16)
    - Cartoons-Cattle, undated (Box 592, Folder 17)
    - Cattle-Angus, 1940s-1960s (Box 592, Folder 18)
    - Cattle-Angus, 1940s-1960s (Box 593, Folder 1)
    - Cattle-Argentina, 1940 (Box 593, Folder 2)
    - Cattle-Brahmans and Zebu, 1931-1949 (Box 593, Folder 3)
    - Cattle-Champions, 1923, 1927 (Box 593, Folder 4)
    - Cattle-Charollaise, undated (Box 593, Folder 5)
    - Cattle-Devons, undated (Box 593, Folder 6)
    - Cattle-Grading and Judging, 1953, undated (Box 593, Folder 7)
    - Cattle-Herefords, 1930s-1950s (Box 593, Folders 8-9)
    - Cattle-Herefords, Bulls, 1920s-1950s (Box 593, Folders 10-11)
    - Cattle-Herefords, Calves, 1950s, undated (Box 594, Folder 1)
    - Cattle-Herefords, Champions, 1950s, undated (Box 594, Folder 2)
    - Cattle-Herefords, Ranch Scenes, 1910s-1960s (Box 594, Folders 3-8)
    - Cattle-Herefords, Ranch Scenes, 1910s-1960s (Box 595, Folder 1)
    - Cattle-Highland, 1921-1954 (Box 595, Folder 2)
    - Cattle-Milk Cows, 1957, undated (Box 595, Folder 3)
    - Cattle-Miscellaneous, undated (Box 595, Folder 4)
    - Cattle-Shorthorns, 1940s-1960s (Box 595, Folder 5)
    - Cattle Fax, undated (Box 595, Folder 6)
    - Cattle Fax Employees, 1970s-1981 (Box 595, Folders 7-14)
    - Cattle Fax Group Shots, June 11, 1980 (Box 595, Folder 15)
    - Cattle in Colorado, University Range between Buena Vista and Salida, 1950 (Box 595, Folder 16)
    - Cattle in Feed Lots, Longmont, CO, February 1947 (Box 595, Folder 17)
    - Cattle in National Forests, 1929-1939 (Box 595, Folder 18)
    - Cattle in New Mexico, June 1948 (Box 595, Folder 19)
    - Cattle in Northern CA, undated (Box 595, Folder 20)
    - Cattle in South Dakota, 1951 (Box 595, Folder 21)
    - Cattle in South Park, Colorado, undated (Box 595, Folder 22)
    - Cattle in South Park and Cripple Creek District, CO, August 1951 (Box 595, Folder 23)
    - Cattle in WY, June 1948, 1951 (Box 595, Folders 24-25)
    - Cattle in WY, Near Douglas, August 1951 (Box 595, Folder 26)
    - Cattle Marketing, 1940s, 1970s (Box 595, Folder 27)
    - Cattle on Del Lichtenberg Ranch, Near Colorado Springs, CO, 1951 (Box 595, Folder 28)
    - Cattle Pictures, 1970s, undated (Box 595, Folder 29)
    - Charles Redd Ranch, La Sal, Utah, 1946 (Box 595, Folder 30)
    - Church in Cuyama, Built by Hubbard Russell, November 1954 (Box 595, Folder 31)
    - Colorado-Junior Colorado Cattlemen Officers, 1953 (Box 595, Folder 32)
    - Colorado Cattlemen’s Association Annual Meeting, Walsenburg, CO, 1952 (Box 595, Folder 33)
    - Colorado Cattlemen’s Association, Regional Meeting, Colorado Springs, CO, December 1951 (Box 595, Folder 34)
    - Colorado Cattlemen’s Quarterly Meeting, Sterling, CO, 1951 (Box 595, Folder 35)
    - Colorado Cattlemen’s Regional Meeting, Steamboat Springs, CO, 1951 (Box 595, Folder 36)
    - Colorado Cattlemen’s Association, Regional Meeting, Montrose, CO, April 4, 1952 (Box 595, Folder 37)
    - Colorado Convention, Canon City, CO, June 1946 (Box 596, Folder 1)
    - Colorado Convention, Steamboat Springs, CO, 1947 (Box 596, Folder 2)
    - Colorado Convention, Boulder, CO, June 1948 (Box 596, Folder 3)
    - Colorado Convention, Grand Junction, CO, June 1949 (Box 596, Folder 4)
    - Colorado Convention, Colorado Springs, CO, May 1952 (Box 596, Folder 5)
    - Colorado Convention, Pueblo, CO, June 1954 (Box 596, Folder 6)
    - Colorado Hereford Association Tour, Gunnison, CO, July 1947 (Box 596, Folder 7)
    - Colorado Hereford Tour, September 1955, undated (Box 596, Folders 8-9)
    - Colorado Ranger Station, San Juan National Forest, CO, 1949 (Box 596, Folder 10)
    - Conrad Schafer Ranch, Hugo, CO, October 1946 (Box 596, Folder 11)
    - Conservation in Utah, August 1948 (Box 596, Folder 12)
    - Contours, 1930s (Box 596, Folder 13)
    - American National Livestock Association-Convention Committee, Baton Rouge, LA, undated (Box 596, Folder 14)
    - Conventions (Groups, Etc.), 1930s-1960s (Box 596, Folders 15-18)
    - Conventions (Groups, Etc.), 1930s-1960s (Box 597, Folders 1-8)
    - Conventions (Groups, Etc.), 1930s-1960s (Box 598, Folders 1-4)
    - Corn-Belt-Dairy Day, 1939-1943 (Box 598, Folder 5)
    - Corn Belt Livestock Feeders, York, NE, Meeting, undated (Box 598, Folder 6)
    - Council of Economic Advisors, 1974 (Box 598, Folder 7)
    - Cowan, Mrs. Ralph, undated (Box 598, Folder 8)
    - Cowbelles-Miscellaneous, 1951-1965 (Box 598, Folder 9)
    - Cowbelles-Alabama, 1959 (Box 598, Folder 10)
    - Cowbelles, undated (Box 598, Folder 11)
    - Cowbelles-California, 1957-1958 (Box 598, Folder 12)
    - Cowbelles-Colorado, undated (Box 598, Folder 13)
    - Cowbelles-Florida, 1963 (Box 598, Folder 14)
    - Cowbelles-Kansas, 1958-1959, undated (Box 598, Folder 15)
    - Cowbelles-Montana, 1954 (Box 598, Folder 16)
    - Cowbelles-National Cowbelles, undated (Box 598, Folder 17)
    - Cowbelles-Nebraska, 1954, undated (Box 598, Folder 18)
    - Cowbelles-Nevada, undated (Box 598, Folder 19)
    - Cowbelles-North Dakota, 1951, 1957 (Box 598, Folder 20)
    - Cowbelles-Oregon, 1954 (Box 598, Folder 21)
    - Cowbelles-South Dakota, undated (Box 598, Folder 22)
    - Cowbelles-Utah, 1956, undated (Box 598, Folder 23)
    - Cowbelles-Washington State, 1957, undated (Box 598, Folder 24)
    - Cowboy and Ice Skater, undated (Box 598, Folder 25)
    - Cowboy Hall of Fame, undated (Box 598, Folder 26)
    - Cowboys, undated (Box 598, Folder 27)
    - Cowboys and Cowgirls, undated (Box 598, Folder 28)
    - Crops, 1937, undated (Box 598, Folder 29)
    - Cuba, 1939-1940, undated (Box 598, Folder 30)
    - Dehorning, 1951 (Box 598, Folder 31)
    - Denver Stockyards, undated (Box 598, Folder 32)
    - Dewey Norell Range, Grand Mesa National Forest, Collbran, Colorado, September 1948 (Box 599, Folder 1)
    - Diseases (Meat-Cattle-Inspection), 1923-1963 (Box 599, Folders 2-3)
    - East Coast Cattlemen’s Chautauqua Tour, 1972-1973 (Box 599, Folder 4)
    - Electronic “Brains,” (Computers), undated (Box 599, Folder 5)
    - England, undated (Box 599, Folder 6)
    - Equipment, 1929-1950s (Box 599, Folders 7-8)
    - Executive Committee, 1949-1973 (Box 599, Folder 9)
    - American National Livestock Association-Executive Committee Meeting, Denver, CO, April 1953 (Box 599, Folder 10)
    - Fauna, 1919, undated (Box 599, Folder 11)
    - Features on Ranches, undated (Box 599, Folder 12)
    - Feed Lots, 1979 (Box 599, Folder 13)
    - Feeders, 1970s, undated (Box 599, Folder 14)
    - Feeding Experiments, 1920s (Box 599, Folder 15)
    - Feeding Yards, 1938-1951 (Box 599, Folder 16)
    - Feeders’ Meet, Denver, CO, April 1955 (Box 599, Folder 17)
    - Fences, 1939, undated (Box 599, Folder 18)
    - Finland, undated (Box 599, Folder 19)
    - Five Mile Ranch, 1890s (Box 599, Folder 20)
    - Florida Convention, Clewiston, FL, November 1951 (Box 599, Folder 21)
    - Florida Convention, St. Petersburg, FL, November 1953 (Box 599, Folder 22)
    - Florida Convention, Panama City, FL, November 1955 (Box 599, Folder 23)
    - Florida Semi-Annual Meeting, Vero Beach, FL, undated (Box 599, Folder 24)
    - Florida State Cattlemen’s Association- Alderman, B.J., President, undated (Box 600, Folder 1)
    - Forest Management Pictures, Paul LaGasse, Bay St. Louis, MS, 1949 (Box 600, Folder 2)
    - Forests, 1912-1948 (Box 600, Folder 3)
    - Fort Hays Experiment Station Field Day, Hays, KS, April 26, 1947 (Box 600, Folder 4)
    - Freighting, 1964, undated (Box 600, Folder 5)
    - Frontier, 1885, undated (Box 600, Folder 6)
    - G.A. Sidwell & Son Ranch, Carr, CO, April 1946 (Box 600, Folder 7)
    - General Council, undated (Box 600, Folder 8)
    - General Council Meeting, August 1952 (Box 600, Folder 9)
    - General Council and Public Relations Committee Meeting, Denver, CO, August 1950 (Box 600, Folder 10)
    - Gilpin-Jefferson Livestock Association, Golden, CO, February 2, 1952 (Box 600, Folder 11)
    - Gophers on Grand Mesa, 1949 (Box 600, Folder 12)
    - Grass and Grazing, 1916-1944 (Box 600, Folders 13-14)
    - Greece, 1946 (Box 600, Folder 15)
    - Gunnison County Meeting, undated (Box 600, Folder 16)
    - Historical Photos, 1800s-1970s (Box 600, Folders 17-18)
    - H.M. Ranch, undated (Box 600, Folder 19)
    - Hoof and Mouth Disease, 1924 (Box 600, Folder 20)
    - Horses, 1924-1948 (Box 601, Folder 1)
    - Horses in Nebraska, May 1948 (Box 601, Folder 2)
    - Horses in New Mexico, June 1948 (Box 601, Folder 3)
    - Horses in Utah, August 1948 (Box 601, Folder 4)
    - Horses in Utah (Northeast Utah), August 1955 (Box 601, Folder 5)
    - Horses in Wyoming, June 1948 (Box 601, Folder 6)
    - Hubert Littler Ranch, Roggen, CO, 1946 (Box 601, Folder 7)
    - Idaho Cattle Tour, August 1952 (Box 601, Folder 8)
    - Idaho Cattlemen’s Tour, August 1948 (Box 601, Folders 9-10)
    - Idaho Tour, 1949, August 1951 (Box 601, Folders 11-12)
    - If and When it Rains, 1934-1937 (Box 601, Folders 13-14)
    - Illinois-Illinois State Fair, 1958 (Box 601, Folder 15)
    - Imports-Exports, 1960s-1970s (Box 601, Folder 16)
    - India, undated (Box 602, Folder 1)
    - Indians, 1941, undated (Box 602, Folder 2)
    - Insects, 1935-1965 (Box 602, Folder 3)
    - Island Park Land and Cattle Company, Ashton, Idaho, 1948 (Box 602, Folder 4)
    - Jack Mansfield Ranch, 1949 (Box 602, Folder 5)
    - Japanese Visitors and YWCA Opening, April 1978 (Box 602, Folder 6)
    - Jesse Harper Ranch, May 1952 (Box 602, Folder 7)
    - Johnson, 1944 (Box 602, Folder 8)
    - Kansas Convention, Topeka, Kansas, March 1950 (Box 602, Folder 9)
    - Kansas Livestock Association, Wichita, KS, March 1949 (Box 602, Folder 10)
    - Kaufman Feed Lots, San Jose, CA, December 1948 (Box 602, Folder 11)
    - Lassen Creek, California, 1948 (Box 602, Folder 12)
    - Leather, 1935, undated (Box 602, Folder 13)
    - Legislative Committee Meeting, Washington, D.C., March 1974 (Box 602, Folder 14)
    - Lincoln County Stockmen’s Association, Meeting in Hugo, CO, November 16, 1951 (Box 602, Folder 15)
    - Louisiana State University, Baton Rouge, LA, 1949 (Box 602, Folder 16)
    - American National Livestock Association-Marketing Committee Meeting, Colorado Springs, CO, May 12, 1954 (Box 602, Folder 17)
    - McDonald Trip to Mexico, 1951 (Box 602, Folder 18)
    - Meat Packers, undated (Box 602, Folder 19)
    - Membership Development, 1977-1980 (Box 602, Folder 20)
    - Mexico, 1932, undated (Box 602, Folder 21)
    - Meyer Brothers Ranch, St. Anthony, Idaho, 1941-1958 (Box 602, Folder 22)
    - Miami Convention Committee, Miami, FL, August 1949 (Box 602, Folder 23)
    - Midland, TX Meeting, August 1949 (Box 602, Folder 24)
    - 1974 Midyear Meeting, Denver, CO, July 1974 (Box 602, Folder 25)
    - Milky Way Farms, Phoenix and Springerville, AZ, September 1946 (Box 602, Folder 26)
    - Miscellaneous Photographs, 1939-1970s, undated (Box 603, Folders 1-4)
    - Mississippi, undated (Box 603, Folder 5)
    - Montana, 1957 (Box 603, Folder 6)
    - Montana Convention, Missoula, Montana, May 1949 (Box 603, Folder 7)
    - Montana Convention, 1951 (Box 603, Folder 8)
    - Montana Convention, Miles City, Montana, May 1954 (Box 603, Folder 9)
    - Montana Convention, undated (Box 603, Folder 10)
    - 1974 Stockgrowers Association Meeting, Billings, Montana, May 1974 (Box 603, Folder 11)
    - Morgan, 1946 (Box 603, Folder 12)
    - N Bar Ranch Sale, Grass Range, Montana, 1951 (Box 603, Folder 13)
    - National Beef Council Meeting, Chicago, IL, April 26, 1955 (Box 603, Folder 14)
    - American National Livestock Association-National Cowbelles Organization Meeting, Denver, CO, August 20, 1951 (Box 603, Folder 15)
    - National Forests, 1907-1945 (Box 603, Folder 16)
    - National Livestock and Meat Board Meeting, Chicago, IL, June 1950 (Box 603, Folder 17)
    - National Livestock Tax Committee, 1947 (Box 603, Folder 18)
    - NCA Building, 1979-1980s (Box 603, Folders 19-20)
    - NCA Communication, 1970s (Box 603, Folder 21)
    - Nebraska, undated (Box 603, Folder 22)
    - Nebraska Convention, Omaha, NE, June 1946 (Box 604, Folder 1)
    - Nebraska Convention, 1947 (Box 604, Folder 2)
    - Nebraska Convention, Omaha, NE, June 1948 (Box 604, Folder 3)
    - Nebraska Convention, Alliance, NE, June 1950 (Box 604, Folder 4)
    - Nebraska Convention, 1951 (Box 604, Folder 5)
    - Nebraska Regional Convention, North Platte, NE, 1951 (Box 604, Folder 6)
    - Nebraska Regional Meeting, Grand Island, NE, April 10, 1952 (Box 604, Folder 7)
    - Nebraska Stockgrowers Association Meeting, Gordon, NE, December 14, 1952 (Box 604, Folder 8)
    - Nevada, undated (Box 604, Folder 9)
    - Nevada Cattlemen’s Association Convention, Elko, Nevada, November 1945 (Box 604, Folder 10)
    - Nevada Cattlemen’s Association, Reno, Nevada, November 1947 (Box 604, Folder 11)
    - Nevada State Cattlemen’s Association, Elko, Nevada, November 1952 (Box 604, Folder 12)
    - Nevada State Cattle Association-Bankofier, Roy, President, November 1954 (Box 604, Folder 13)
    - New Mexico Cattle Growers Association-Hening, Horace, 1948 (Box 604, Folder 14)
    - New Mexico Executive Committee Meeting, Raton, New Mexico, December 1945 (Box 604, Folder 15)
    - New Mexico Executive Committee Meeting, Clovis, New Mexico, 1946 (Box 604, Folder 16)
    - New Mexico Quarterly Meeting, Raton, New Mexico, June 1947 (Box 604, Folder 17)
    - New Mexico Quarterly Meeting, Albuquerque, New Mexico, September 1947 (Box 604, Folder 18)
    - New Mexico Quarterly Meetings, Clayton, New Mexico, June 1948, June 1951 (Box 604, Folders 19-20)
    - New Mexico Quarterly Meeting, Gallup, New Mexico, September 1951 (Box 604, Folder 21)
    - Nixon, Richard M., January 27, 1970 (Box 604, Folder 22)
    - Norman Smith Ranch, Angus Cattle, March 1951 (Box 604, Folder 23)
    - Norris Cattle Company, Ocala, FL, 1949 (Box 604, Folder 24)
    - North Dakota, 1941, undated (Box 604, Folder 25)
    - North Dakota Convention, Bismarck, North Dakota, June 1946 (Box 604, Folder 26)
    - North Dakota Convention, Williston, North Dakota, 1947 (Box 604, Folder 27)
    - North Dakota Conventions, Minot, North Dakota, May 1948, June 1949 (Box 604, Folders 28-29)
    - North Dakota Convention, Dickinson, North Dakota, undated (Box 605, Folder 1)
    - North Park Stockgrowers Association, Walden, CO, June 7, 1952, June 1955 (Box 605, Folders 2-3)
    - Northeastern New Mexico Cattle Growers Association, Raton, New Mexico, March 6, 1946 (Box 605, Folder 4)
    - Northern Arizona Cattlemen’s Association, 1946 (Box 605, Folder 5)
    - Northern California Tour, August-September 1950, September 1953 (Box 605, Folders 6-7)
    - Northern New Mexico Livestock Association, Springer, New Mexico, 1951 (Box 605, Folder 8)
    - Northern New Mexico Livestock Association, Cimarron, New Mexico, March 15, 1952 (Box 605, Folder 9)
    - Northwest Oklahoma Cattlemen’s Association, 1946 (Box 605, Folder 10)
    - Northwest Oklahoma Cattlemen’s Association, Woodward, OK, May 1948, May 1950, May 8, 1952, May 1954 (Box 605, Folders 11-14)
    - Oda Mason Ranch, Near Laramie, WY, undated (Box 605, Folder 15)
    - Oddities, 1935, 1955 (Box 605, Folder 16)
    - American National Livestock Association-Office Staff, October 1948 (Box 605, Folder 17)
    - Ogle County (Illinois) Feeders Association, April 1955 (Box 605, Folder 18)
    - Ohio Cattle Feeders, undated (Box 605, Folder 19)
    - Oklahoma, 1938, 1958 (Box 605, Folder 20)
    - Old Cowboy Photos, undated (Box 605, Folder 21)
    - Omaha Stockyards, 1956 (Box 605, Folder 22)
    - Oregon Cattlemen’s Association, Prineville, Oregon, May 1952 (Box 605, Folder 23)
    - Oregon Convention, Enterprise, Oregon, May 1946 (Box 605, Folder 24)
    - Oregon Convention, 1951 (Box 605, Folder 25)
    - Oregon Convention, Corvallis, Oregon, May 1954 (Box 605, Folder 26)
    - Overgrazing, 1931, 1945 (Box 605, Folder 27)
    - Owyhee County Meeting, Silver City, Idaho, July 1953 (Box 605, Folder 28)
    - Panama, undated (Box 605, Folder 29)
    - Peru, undated (Box 605, Folder 30)
    - Philippines, undated (Box 605, Folder 31)
    - Pigs, 1922-1941 (Box 605, Folder 32)
    - Plains, undated (Box 605, Folder 33)
    - Poisonous Plants, undated (Box 605, Folder 34)
    - Ports of Entry, undated (Box 605, Folder 35)
    - Posts, undated (Box 605, Folder 36)
    - Prairie Dog Town, undated (Box 605, Folder 37)
    - Predators, 1923-1924, undated (Box 605, Folder 38)
    - Presidents, 1898-1981 (Box 606, Folder 1)
    - Public Land Committee Congressional Hearing, September 1947 (Box 606, Folder 2)
    - Public Lands Council, undated (Box 606, Folder 3)
    - Public Lands Meeting, Salt Lake City, Utah, August 1946 (Box 606, Folder 4)
    - American National Livestock Association-Public Relations Committee, 1950 (Box 606, Folder 5)
    - American National Livestock Association-Public Relations and Executive Committee Meetings, Denver, CO, February 27, 1952 (Box 606, Folder 6)
    - Purebred Cattle, undated (Box 606, Folder 7)
    - Ranch Operations, 1970s, undated (Box 606, Folder 8)
    - Record of Performance-Cattle, 1943, 1953 (Box 606, Folder 9)
    - Regional Cattlemen’s Association, Garden of the Gods, August 1951 (Box 606, Folder 10)
    - American National Livestock Association-Research Committee Meeting, Denver, CO, undated (Box 606, Folder 11)
    - Reseedings, 1944-1948 (Box 606, Folder 12)
    - Rio Blanco Farmers and Stockgrowers Association, Meeker, CO, 1951 (Box 606, Folder 13)